rdi.co.uk 2018-12-26

# Privacy Policy | Arden University

## Our Privacy Policy

Welcome to the Global University Systems Privacy notice.

Global University Systems, a trading name of Global University Systems B.V. and its subsidiary companies, including Arden University Limited respects your privacy and is committed to protecting your personal data. This privacy notice tells you how we look after your personal data when you visit our websites (regardless of where you visit from) and tells you about your privacy rights and how the law protects you.

Please use the Glossary at section 12 for the meaning of some of the terms used in this privacy notice.

PURPOSE OF THIS PRIVACY NOTICE

This privacy notice aims to give you information on how Global University Systems collects and processes your personal data including any data you may provide through this website when you:

  * Arrive on our website from a social media site such as Facebook Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat, Pinterest, VKontakte or LinkedIn;
  * Complete a call back / enquiry form;
  * You register on our site to apply for a course or programme, corporate/ executive education, professional training, (online, distance learning or campus based) and whether you are applying for yourself or for employees or other staff at your organisation which may be or become a customer of ours;
  * Sign up for marketing materials; or
  * You provide us with your personal data by any other means.

This website is not intended for children and we do not knowingly collect data relating to children on this website. However, where GUS processes personal data of children in its business operations, we ensure that appropriate safeguards and consents are obtained from parents or caregivers as applicable [and that we follow relevant guidance from the Information Commissioner’s Office in relation to the processing of children’s data]. You may contact legal@gus.global for further information about this.

It is important that you read this privacy notice together with any other privacy notice or fair processing notice we may provide on specific occasions when we are collecting or processing personal data about you so that you are fully aware of how and why we are using your data.

This privacy notice supplements the other notices and does not replace them.

  * View our full Cookie Policy
  * View our Refer a Friend Policy
  * View our Refund Policy for EU Residents
  * View our Refund Policy for Non-EU Residents

1\. IMPORTANT INFORMATION AND WHO WE ARE

2\. THE DATA WE COLLECT ABOUT YOU

3\. HOW IS YOUR PERSONAL DATA COLLECTED?

4\. HOW WE USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA 

5\. PURPOSES FOR WHICH WE WILL USE YOUR PERSONAL DATA

6\. HOW WE USE SENSITIVE PERSONAL INFORMATION (SPECIAL CATEGORY DATA)

7\. DISCLOSURES OF YOUR PERSONAL DATA

8\. INTERNATIONAL TRANSFERS

## Contact

Questions, comments and requests regarding this Privacy Policy are welcomed and should be addressed to [dpo@arden.ac.uk](mailto:info@arden.ac.uk)

OR

FAO Data Protection Officer  
Arden House, Middlemarch Park, Coventry, CV3 4FJ
